export const quizData = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: `React is mainly used for building ___`,
      options: [`Database`, `Connectivity`, `User interface`,`Design Platform`],
      answer: `User interface`
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: `The lifecycle methods are mainly used for ___`,
      options: [`keeping track of event history`, `enhancing components`, `freeing up resources`,`none of the above`],
      answer: `freeing up resources`
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: `___ can be done while multiple elements need to be returned from a component.`,
      options: [` Abstraction`, `Packing`, `Insulation`,`Wrapping`],
      answer: `Wrapping`
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: `Which of the following methods in a React Component should be overridden to stop the component from updating?`,
      options: [`willComponentUpdate`, `shouldComponentUpdate`, `componentDidUpdate`,`componentDidMount`],
      answer: `shouldComponentUpdate`
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: `What is used to pass data to a component from outside?`,
      options: [`setState`, `render with arguments`, `PropTypes`,`props`],
      answer: `props`
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: `Which of the following methods in a React Component is called after the component is rendered for the first time?`,
      options: [`componentDidUpdate`, `componentDidMount`, `componentMounted`,`componentUpdated`],
      answer: `componentDidMount`
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: `What will happen if you call setState() inside render() method?`,
      options: [`Repetitive output appears on the screen`, `Duplicate key error`, `Stack overflow error`,`Nothing happens`],
      answer: `Stack overflow error`
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: `Ref is used for referring an element or component returned by ___`,
      options: [`react()`, `render()`, `reduce()`,`refer()`],
      answer: `render()`
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: `What are the two ways that data gets handled in React?`,
      options: [`state & props`, `services & components`],
      answer: `state & props`
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: `What are the two ways that data gets handled in React?`,
      options: [`Keys`, `Props`, `Elements`,`Ref`],
      answer: `Props`
    }
    
    
  ];
  